(忆往昔)
-停下  -不是利维坦
- Stop! Stop! Stop! - Not leviathans.
你们去哪了
What the hell happened to you guys?
我去了炼狱  萨姆撞了狗
I went to purgatory. Sam hit a dog.
克劳力抓走了你  我看到了
Crowley kidnapped you. I saw that.
但你逃出来了  怎么逃的
But you escaped. How?
那里有块碑
There was a tablet.
我跟克劳力说我要开启地狱之门
I told Crowley I was opening a hell gate,
但我读的是另一个章节
but I was reading from another chapter --
如何杀死恶魔
how to destroy demons.
-你好  妈妈  -凯文
- Hi, mom.  - Kevin!
她没问题
She's clean.
这位可爱的女士是谁
Who is this lovely young thing?
离我儿子远一点
Stay away from my son.
你们好  孩子们
Hello, boys.
没了这个  看你们怎么
Good luck closing the gates to hell...
关上地狱之门
without this.
-凯文  -开什么玩笑
- Kevin! - You've got to be kidding me!
我们没了石碑
Since we lost the tablet,
凯文觉得我们不需要他了
Kevin figures we don't need him.
没错  但是克劳力有石碑
Yeah, but Crowley still does.
你是天使吗  你们为石碑而来吗
You're an angel? You're chasing the magic rock?
我们负责保护神之语
We protect the word of God.
小卡没能逃出来
Cass didn't make it.
迪恩
Dean!
(如今)
推我  使劲儿推  高一点儿
Push me! Push me! Higher!
这是手指画  亚伦  不是身体画
It's finger painting, Aaron, not body painting.
我们去洗干净
Let's get you cleaned up.
进去吧
There you go.
[邪恶力量 第8季第7集]
(双松度假村 距此10公里)
你来了
Hey.
来了
你看起来就像是...
You look like you've s--
我本来想说  "你就像是活见鬼了"
Well, I was gonna say, "You look like you've seen a ghost,"
但很可能是嗨过头了  没事吧
but you'd probably be stoked. Uh, you okay?
我没事  有什么事情吗
Yeah, I'm cool. What's up?
这个孩子从幼儿园失踪了
Well, this kid went missing from a preschool.
真糟糕  还有呢
That sucks. And?
在他失踪的同时
And at the same time he vanished,
一场莫名的龙卷风来袭  持续了20秒
a surprise tornado hit, lasted maybe 20 seconds,
然后又迅速消失
then, uh...shazam!
风过天晴
Back to perfect weather.
还有人藐视气候变化呢
Hmm. And they pooh-pooh climate change.
是啊
Yeah.
过去几周内  同样的怪事儿
Well, similar wackiness has happened
在别处也时有发生
over the past few weeks in other places --
在塔尔萨  一名巴士司机消失了
Uh, Tulsa, a bus driver vanishes
而河里挤满了青蛙
and a river gets overrun with frogs.
新墨西哥州一名邮差失踪了
New Mexico -- a mailman disappears,
地面塌陷了
the earth splits open.
这样啊  你觉得是恶魔干的
All right. So, uh, you thinking demons?
是啊  有可能  但是
Yeah, possibly, but...
这些事件发生的范围太大
I mean, this stuff was major.
当事人没有任何相同之处
These folks have nothing in common --
宗教信仰不同  家乡不同  年龄各异
No religious affiliations, different hometowns, all ages.
为什么恶魔要抓走他们
Why would demons want them?
恶魔想要什么都很奇怪
Why do demons want anything?
我们要去管吗
Uh, so, we on this?
是
Yep.
你到底要什么
What do you want?!
我把所有的名字都告诉你了
I've given you all the names.
不对不对  根本不对
No. No. No. And no.
那不是我想要听的
That's not what I want to hear.
比起我  这个伤你更深
This hurts you more than it hurts me,
所以我可以持续到永远
so I can go on forever.
而对你而言  永远即意味着...
Which, in your case, forever means...
天荒地老
Well, forever.
等天使们发现你的所作所为后...
When the angels find out what you're doing...
那又怎样  把我撵走
They'll be what -- put out?
我好怕怕啊  真的
I'm quaking, really.
天堂的电网都已经彻底毁了
The power grid is so whacked out in heaven,
他们都没发现你失踪了
they don't even know you're not there.
我现在数三下
So, on the count of 3...
一  二
1, 2...
你还没数三呢
What happened to 3?
我说谎了  我常这样
I lied. I do that.
把其他的名字都告诉我
Just give me the other names.
没有了
There are no other names!
下一代还未出生
The next generation isn't born yet.
真的吗
Truth?
千真万确
Truth.
这样的话  就没理由继续折磨你了
Well, I suppose there's no reason to keep torturing you, then.
对不住了
Sorry.
一旦开始  就很难收手
Once you get going, it's really hard to stop.
给我把他看好了
Keep him on ice.
从他嘴里我们只得到了皮毛而已
We've only just scratched the surface with this one.
希望这个大厅里的喧闹不要太让你们烦心
I hope the ruckus down the hall wasn't too off-putting.
现在的建筑标准跟宗教法庭时期可不一样了
Construction standards aren't what they were during the Inquisition.
明白了
I see.
没时间说细节了  那就这样吧
No niceties. All right, then.
你们肯定在想  我为何要召集一队杂牌军
I suppose you're wondering why I convened this motley group.
妈妈
Mom!
别在我出门回来时都用圣水泼我
You've got to stop drowning me in holy water every time I go out!
我没被恶魔附身
I'm not possessed!
暂时没有而已
Not yet. Not now.
他们上了我的身  你忘了吗
They got to me, remember?
我们有魔法袋  恶魔看不见我们
We've got hex bags that make us invisible to demons.
到处都画了恶魔陷阱
We've got demon traps painted everywhere!
手臂上还纹了个魔符
I've got a sigil tattooed on my arm!
如果我们不停地换地方  肯定没事的
If we just keep moving, we'll be fine!
继续住在老鼠成灾的破屋子里
What, and keep living in rat-infested hovels
时刻躲避着那些邪恶之物
and running from cursed creatures?!
这哪叫生活
This is no life!
这就是我的生活
It's my life.
倒霉当先知的是我
I'm the one dragging the prophet load.
抱歉我拖累了你
I'm sorry I pulled you into it.
不要抱歉  要做好准备
Don't be sorry. Be ready.
我们必须停止逃跑  开始反击
We've got to stop running and start taking a stand.
那可是痴人说梦
Okay, you know that's crazy.
才不是呢
No, it's not!
只要有你在克劳力的恶魔身上用过的炸弹
Not if we have the bomb you used on Crowley's demons.
找做那东西的材料得跑遍全世界
The thing I made had ingredients from all over the world.
知道吗  派了一群恶魔才找齐的
All right? Demons had to get the stuff.
所以我才找了专家
That's why I went to an expert.
什么  谁
What? Who?
我雇了一个巫师
I hired a witch.
-巫师  广告网站上找的
- A witch? - Off of craigslist.
她叫黛尔塔·梅朵塔  聪明伶俐
Her name is Delta Mendota, and she is a smart cookie.
有斗志  靠得住  不怕杀人
She's scrappy, reliable, and she's willing to kill.
听着  我是你妈  我做这些都是为了你
Look, I'm your mother, and I did this for you.
你凭什么认定她可信
What makes you think you can trust her?
我不信她
I don't.
所以我没有告诉她准确的用量
That's why I didn't give her the exact quantities
以及怎样混合
or tell her how to blend them.
她都不知道
She's in the dark.
你告诉她我们在做恶魔炸弹
You told her we were making demon bombs!
对啊  这让她变得特别积极
Yeah, and that got her super motivated.
黛尔塔汇报进度的时间到了
Oh! Time for Delta to check in.
我的老天
Oh, my God.
你好  谭夫人
Hi, Mrs. Tran.
那是你儿子吗
Is that your son?
你好  凯文
Hi, Kevin.
你好  黛尔塔  我们说正事
Hi, Delta. Bring us up to speed.
东西备齐了吗
You've got all the stuff?
差不多了
Almost.
我猜你不打算告诉我炸弹配方
I don't suppose you'd tell me the recipe for these bombs?
你知道规矩
You know the rules.
"随遇"  意思就是你不可以问问题
"Casual encounters." That means no questions asked.
妈  那是另一条广告了
No, mom, that's another part of craigslist.
你做巫师多久了
How long have you been a witch?
全职巫师吗
A full witch?
乐队解散之后
Since the band broke up.
你还参加过乐队
You were in a band?
你们听我说
Look, guys.
我对待巫术生意非常认真
I take my witch business real serious.
我会全力以赴  一定是最棒的巫术
I'm on it, and it's gonna be wicked awesome.
好了吗
Okay?
夏甲夫人吗  探员罗斯和马洛伊
Mrs. Hagar? Mm-hmm. Agents Roth and Malloy.
我们想跟你谈谈亚伦·韦伯绑架案
We want to speak to you about Aaron Webber's abduction.
我都跟警察说过了
Like I told the police,
前一秒我正带亚伦去洗手
one minute I was taking Aaron to get cleaned up,
下一秒
and the next minute...
我在三个街区之外的停车场醒来
I woke up in a park three blocks away.
你完全不记得发生了什么事
And you have no memory of what happened?
是的  他就那样失踪了
No. He was just gone.
能想到有什么人想伤害他吗
Can you think any reason why somebody would want to harm him?
任何的敌人
Um, any enemies?
敌人  他才五岁
Enemies? He's 5.
[拉丁语]
他说什么
Excuse me?
为了你的安全使用的代码
It's, uh, code for your own safety
保证你不会在强化审讯时泄露信息
so that you can't reveal anything under enhanced interrogation.
您醒来的时候
Now, when you woke up on the floor,
周围有打斗的痕迹吗
were there any signs of struggle?
没有
No.
硫磺的味道
Smell like sulfur?
你们怎么知道
How did you know that?
猜测而已  多谢您的配合
Lucky guess. Thanks for your time.
对驱魔咒无反应
No reaction to the exorcism.
对  现在没有被附身
Yeah, not possessed at the moment.
但是我敢打赌亚伦·韦伯在恶魔手里
But I'm willing to bet a demon got ahold of Aaron Webber.
(突发风暴  一名儿童失踪)
迪恩
Dean?
怎么了  你没事吧
What's going on? Are you all right?
不知道
I don't know.
我刚刚看到了什么
I just saw something.
看到了什么
Uh, you saw what?
小卡
Cass.
Cass?
哪里
Where?
就在外面
Right there.
还有之前在路边
And -- and -- and earlier, on the road.
我好像看到他了
I feel like I'm seeing him.
那不可能啊
That's...not possible.
是你自己说的
I mean, you said it yourself.
你出来了  他没能出来
You made it out and he didn't, right?
我费尽力气就想让大家一起出来
I tried so damn hard to get us the hell out of there.
你知道你尽力了
I know you did.
知道吗  我本可以把他拉出来的
You know, I could have pulled him out.
我就是不明白他为什么不再加把劲
I just don't understand why he didn't try harder.
迪恩
Dean.
你已经尽力了
You did everything you could.
对  可是为什么我还这么难受
Yeah, but why do I feel like crap?
幸存者的内疚
Survivor's guilt?
要是你放任不管  它会一直折磨你
If you let it, this is gonna keep messing with you.
你必须从内疚中走出来
You got to walk past it.
就快到了
We're getting close.
真的吗  我什么也看不见
Really? I don't see crap.
那个出口到底长什么样啊
I mean, what the hell is this escape hatch supposed to look like?
他不知道
He doesn't know.
你让我刀山火海一路走到这
Hey, you just drug me through the fire.
拜托给个准话
Please tell me you know.
它就在这  他们保证的
It's here. They promised.
他们  真让人放心
Oh, they? Well, that's comforting.
即便它真的存在
Well, even if it does exist...
我刚问过了  小卡
Broken record, Cass.
迪恩  这是一条人类通道
Dean, it's a human portal.
还没有证据显示天使能够通过...
There's still no proof that an angel can pass --
忍着吧  小卡  你非来不可  就这么办
Stow it, Cass. You're coming. That's final.
我只是说
I'm just saying...
万一行不通
If it doesn't work...
谢谢你所做的一切
...thank you for everything.
把标记留住
Save the hallmark.
好吗
Okay?
会成功的 不会有谁被落下
It's gonna work. Nobody gets left behind.
希望这里的橙汁和薄煎饼还符合你们的口味
Hope you enjoyed our orange juice and pancakes.
这种碳水化合物最好是早餐吃
Best to pack in those carbs in the morning, you know.
-我们是在太空飞船上吗  -你说什么
- Are we on a spaceship? - Sorry?
把我们从家里  从亲人身边劫走
Snapping us up from our homes, our families,
然后传送到这艘母舰上
teleporting us to this m-mother ship.
-母舰  -你们是外星人  对吧
- Mother ship? - You're aliens, right?
我这话大概问了也白问
Possibly a long shot.
你们认识这个东西吗
Does this mean anything to you?
我不认识汉字
I don't read Chinese.
美国人还真是日渐低级了
Talk about the dumbing down of America.
有人认识吗  很有意思的  试试嘛
Anyone? Come on. It's fun. Give it a go.
你们这群笨蛋完全不知道这是什么对吧
You hapless toads are utterly clueless, aren't you?
我家里还有老婆孩子
I-I-I got a wife and kids.
我有一堆账单要付  工作耽误不起
I-I got bills. I can't miss work.
-先生  -我有自己的权利
- Sir. - I got rights!
我不是可以打一个电话吗
Where's my one phone call?
还有谁想发牢骚吗
Anyone else want to complain?
"我们保存着这个..."
"We hold this..."
可能是"这些"
Um, maybe "these."
"真相..."
"...truths to be..."
对
Oh. Oh, right.
这样好认多了
That's -- that's better, yeah.
你好  你叫凯文是吧
Hi. Kevin, right?
我刚才...
So, I was -- ohh!
搞什么
What the hell?!
这是我妈  你们见过
And my mother, you've met.
是啊
Yeah.
东西你都准备好了吗
You have everything?
那当然  虽说挺难搞  不过还是值得的
You bet. It was a bitch, but so worth it.
说实话  那群恶魔不把我当人看
Honestly, I am sick of being treated like dirt
我实在受不了
by those demons.
谁死了之后他们就成大王了
Like, who died and made them boss?
可能真的有人死了
Well, probably somebody did.
不过他们那种蛮横的态度真该收敛一下了
But they could use a serious attitude reduction.
小凯  卫生间在哪儿
Kev, where's the ladies room?
我开了很久的车  还被你妈...
Long drive, and, you know...
-在那边  -好的
- Over there. - Cool.
黛尔塔  这是什么玩意
Delta, what is this?!
我说得很清楚  我要建一座军火库
I was clear. I need to build an arsenal.
这也就顶多算是一件武器
This maybe gets me one weapon!
等你付我全款之后  我再把剩下的货交给你
It's just a little taste of what you'll get when I get paid in full.
当初可不是这么约定的
That was not the agreement!
现在是了
It is now.
凯文
Kevin!
省省吧
Forget it!
现在不仅有美国人失踪
Hey, so it's not just Americans who are vanishing.
有个家伙  叫路易吉·庞氏
Uh, this guy, Luigi Ponzi
在罗马地铁的两节车厢之间走着走着就消失了
disappeared walking between two subway cars in Rome.
而在地面之上发生了雹暴
And right above ground, there was a freak hail storm.
我们要去罗马吗
So, we going to Rome?
应该还不错
Wouldn't be too shabby.
你好  迪恩
Hello, Dean.
太不可思议了  伙计  我简直不敢相信
Unbelievable, man. I-I cannot believe it.
你真的就在我面前
You're actually here.
是啊  我一直想跟你们联系
Yeah, I've been trying to reach out.
但不知什么原因  我的能量不够强
But for whatever reason, I wasn't at full power.
所以联系不上你们
So I couldn't connect with you.
所以你才一直看到他
That must have been why you kept seeing him.
你觉得呢
I mean, you think?
是啊
Yeah.
说实话
Yeah, uh, I got to be honest.
我在想你到底是怎么出来的
I-I-I'm thinking, how the hell did you make it out?
我也去过那里  我了解那个地方
I mean, I -- I was there. I-I-I know that place.
我知道要不断地挣扎探索
I know how we had to scratch and claw
要杀戮流血
and kill and bleed
找到那个通道并穿越过去
to find that portal and make it through it,
我为了出来差点送命
and it almost finished me.
所以...
So, uh...
你到底是怎么活着出来的
So how exactly are you sitting here with us right now?
迪恩  你刚才所说的一点都没错
Dean, everything you just said is completely true.
而这正是奇怪之处
And that's the strange part.
我不知道
I...have no idea.
我只记得不停地奔跑  躲避利维坦
I remember endlessly running and hiding from Leviathan,
然后我就出现在了伊利诺伊州的一条公路旁
and then I was on the side of the road in Illinois.
就是这样
And...that was it.
就这样
And that -- that was it?
对
Yes.
我身上很脏
Oh. I'm dirty.
是啊  在炼狱待过确实会这样
Yeah, well, purgatory will do that to you.
也许你被骗了  根本就没有裂缝
Maybe you were lied to. Maybe there is no seam.
都是我骗别人  没人骗得了我
I lie. I don't get lied to.
你们难道不是信心满满吗
Aren't you guys all about faith?
算不上吧
Not particularly.
凡事还是要有信心啊
Oh, ye of frigging little faith.
到底怎么回事
What the hell?
就在那边  它在对你做出回应
There it is. It's reacting to you.
准备好了吗  就像我们之前说好的
All right. Ready? Just like we talked about.
我可全靠你了  哥们
Putting a lot of trust in you, brother.
这是你应得的
You earned it.
我们那边再见
I'll see you on the other side.
[咒语]
走吧
Let's go.
迪恩  等等
Dean, wait.
迪恩
Dean?
怎么了
Huh?
你还好吧
You all right?
你看出这事相当不对劲了吧
You do see something severely wrong here, right?
萨姆  离开那个鬼地方的过程
Sammy, I remember every second
我记得一清二楚
of leaving that place.
我记得那种灼热  恶臭  疼痛  恐惧
I mean, I remember the heat, the stink, the pain, the fear.
整个痛苦的经历都留在我脑海里
I have that whole ugly mess right here,
可他却说不记得是怎么出来的了
and he says he has no idea how he got out?
我才不信
I -- I'm just not buying it.
那你觉得他在撒谎
So you think he's lying?
我的意思是肯定有别的事情发生
I'm saying something else happened.
我看到他当时那种虚弱的状态了
I saw the shape that he was in.
我是说他不可能靠自己一人杀出来
I mean, there was no way he was fighting his ass out alone.
不可能
No way.
好吧  那么
All right. So...
是谁或什么帮他逃出来的
Who or what got him out?
肯定是
Exactly.
好点了吗
Better?
听着  你这个小贱货
Listen, you little skank.
在服务行业
In the service industry,
都是先到货才付款
you always deliver the goods, then you get paid.
连妓女都懂这些
Even hookers know that.
那是你这么觉得
Hmm. Says you.
我妹妹就是妓女
See, my sister's a hooker.
所以妓女先拿到钱  然后才交货
So hookers get paid first, and then you get the goods.
反正没有恶魔来追杀我
Look, I'm not the one with demons on my ass.
你想反悔我们的交易  我无所谓
You want to renege on our deal, it's fine by me.
凯文  把我的钱包拿来
Kevin, bring me my purse.
你妈一定为你感到骄傲
Your mother must be so proud.
确实
She is.
当然和我妹妹一起  酒吧生意不是很火
Of course, with my sister, the bar ain't real high.
妈  是你把储藏室窗户边的盐线破开了吗
Mom! Did you break the salt line by the store-room window?
什么  当然不是
What?! Of course not!
别白费劲了  凯文
I wouldn't bother, Kevin.
你们跑不掉的
There's no rush.
你好  黛尔塔
Hello, Delta.
你出卖了我们
You betrayed us?
你怎么能这样
How could you?
我很随机善变
I'm mercurial.
恐怕黛尔塔会觉得你是一个
I'm afraid Delta found you to be
很难相处又不领情的雇主  谭女士
a difficult and ungrateful employer, Mrs. Tran.
她觉得如果和我谈生意的话会赚得更多一些
She felt she'd gain far more leverage by negotiating with me.
毕竟我是地狱之王
I am, after all, the king of hell.
而你只是位母亲
And you are a mom.
我表现得很好  对吧  陛下
I did good, didn't I, your majesty?
是的  很好
Yes, very.
冒昧的愚弄
Presumptuous twit.
求你了  把我抓走  放了我儿子吧
Please. Take me. Leave my son alone.
抓你  我抓你有什么用啊
You? What would I do with you?
杀了她  毁了做咒语用的材料
Kill her. Destroy the makings for the spell.
-不要  -和老妈说再见吧
- No! - Yes. Say goodbye to mommy.
有什么新消息
What's the latest?
什么新消息也没有
The latest is nothing.
就像一切都停了
It's like it all stopped.
没有任何与离奇的自然事件有关的离奇失踪
No freak disappearances linked to any freak natural events.
那么现在有多少人失踪了  七个
So how many have we got, seven?
是的  路易吉  贾斯汀  亚伦  玛丽亚
Yeah, uh, Luigi, Justin, Aaron, Maria...
玛丽亚  丹尼斯  克里斯塔  斯文
Maria, Dennis, Krista, Sven.
我真想念电视机
I missed television.
等一下  小卡  你怎么知道那些人名的
Wait, Cass. How did you know those are the names?
-他们都是先知  -先知
- Well, they're prophets. - Prophets?
是的  天使天生就知道所有先知的名字
Yeah, angels instinctively know the names of every prophet,
过去的  现在的还有将来的
past, present, and future.
那么这是所有现存的先知的名单
So this list is the name of every one of them that exists?
是的  直到下一代诞生
Yes, until the next generation is born.
当然还有凯文·谭
Plus Kevin Tran, of course.
由于一个时段内只能存在一个先知
The other seven are future prophets,
另外那七个是未来的先知
Since, uh, only one can exist at a time.
既然恰克是先知  凯文怎么也是先知
How is Kevin a prophet if Chuck is a prophet?
我不清楚恰克怎么了  但是
I'm not sure what happened to Chuck, but, um...
他肯定死了
he must be dead.
如果凯文死了就会有下一个来接班
So, the next one comes off the bench if Kevin goes down?
没错
Exactly.
当然他们不知道自己的身份
And they have no idea who they are, of course.
克劳力
Crowley.
保险起见  他要绝望了
Insurance. boy, he's getting desperate.
这能解释所有的离奇现象
Explains all the weird phenomena.
低等恶魔能劫持重型货船
Lower-level demons nabbing heavy-duty cargo.
神之语的躯壳
The vessels of God's Word...Boom.
我能感觉到有事情要发生
I get the feeling something's going on.
你好
Hello.
谭夫人
Mrs. Tran?
你们到底在...
Well, where the hell have you...
什么
What?
克劳力抓走了凯文
Crowley's got Kevin.
凯文  正如你所见
So, Kevin, as you can see,
我们之间的关系现在更明了了
our relationship is much simpler now.
你要么帮我  要么就死
You either help me, or you die,
然后这些人中就会有人接你的班
and one of these fine specimens takes your place.
我不太明白你为什么还要犹豫
I don't quite understand your hesitation.
你刚刚杀了我妈妈
You just killed my mother.
非常不幸
Very unfortunate.
但是她也在策划杀我和我的手下
But to be fair, she was plotting to kill me and my kind.
凯文
Kevin.
Kev.
我可以和你这样勇敢的小伙子做一笔交易
I can do a great deal for a plucky lad like you.
我一旦读出了石碑你就会杀了我
You'll just kill me as soon as I read the tablet.
所有的年轻人都这么愤世嫉俗吗
Are all young people so horribly cynical?
你让我很沮丧  凯文
It depresses me, Kevin.
事情是这样的
Here's the thing.
我真的很想让你读出这块石碑
I really want you to read the tablet
因为坦白地说  这东西很没有希望
because, frankly, this lot fail to inspire.
然而  俗话说得好
However, better a stupid prophet
做头蠢驴也别做倔驴
than a stubborn prophet, as the saying goes.
你选择当哪个
So what's it gonna be?
也许你怀疑我不是动真格的
Perhaps you doubt that I'm serious?
那么
So...
最近读过什么好的石碑吗
Read any good tablets lately?
她到底在哪
Where the hell is she?
她会来的
She'll be here.
96英里标志牌应该在公路的一半
Look, mile marker 96 was kind of the halfway point.
我们要赶快走
We got to move!
通道要关上了
The portal's closing!
小卡  加把劲
Cass! Damn it! Come on!
不
No.
赶快
Come on!
我抓住你了  坚持住
I got you! Hold on!
迪恩
Dean!
坚持住
Hold on!
迪恩
Dean!
小卡  出去聊两句
Cass, can I talk to you outside?
什么
What?
没错  什么
Exactly. What?
到底发生了什么
What the hell happened?
在炼狱的时候
Back there. Purgatory.
我说了要带你出来
I told you I would get you out.
我们都快成功了
We were there!
而你似乎就那么放弃了
It was like you just gave up.
你好像不相信我们可以出来
It's like you didn't believe we could do it.
你先前就一直在说  我们这样是徒劳的
I mean, you kept saying that you didn't think it would work.
你不相信我吗
Did you not trust me?!
-迪恩  -为了把你救出来  我尽了全力
- Dean... - I did everything I could to get you out -- everything!
我没有丢下你
I did not leave you.
你觉得这是你的错吗
So you think this was your fault?
你们能帮忙  对吧
You can do this, can't you?
你们能救他回来
You can get him back?
克劳力是怎么找到你们的
How did Crowley find you?
我雇了个巫师  她出卖了我们
Oh, I hired a witch, and she ratted us out.
巫师
A witch?!
为什么要雇巫师
Why'd you hire a witch?
当然是为了制作恶魔炸弹
To make demon bombs, of course!
这是凯文的笔记本
These are Kevin's notes.
你能想到克劳力带他去哪里了吗
You have any idea where Crowley took him?
不知道  不过
No. But, uh...
这家伙也许知道
This guy might.
说吧
Let's talk.
人少一点  你大概更愿意开口
I thought privacy might make it easier to chat.
是时候决定了  凯文
Decision time, Kevin.
你准备怎么做
How's this going to go?
不要顽抗  凯文
Don't be recalcitrant, Kevin.
否则我这脾气又要使坏了
You know it brings out the worst in me.
好吧  够了
All right! Enough!
我做
I'll do it!
接下来是"恶魔
The next is... "The demonic influence
对灵魂之毯的影响"
on the collective tapestry of the soul."
全是废话
Blah, blah, blah.
这玩意就没人整理过吗
Doesn't anyone ever edit this stuff?
到目前为止  神写的东西真没劲
So far, as a writer, God's a snooze.
估计是聚会不好玩
No fun at parties, I hear.
"流放到地狱的恶魔囚犯"
Um, "Demonic transport to the regions of hell."
说点我不知道的
Tell me something I don't know!
要宏观上的  这些太鸡毛蒜皮了
Think macro. This is stupefyingly micro.
-多宏观  -改变游戏规则的那种
- How macro? - Game changing.
抱歉  谭夫人
Sorry, Mrs. Tran.
等等  你做什么
Wait! What?!
是这儿吗
This it?
是的
Yes.
我儿子在里面
My son is in there!
所以克劳力已经很不好对付了
Which means Crowley already has leverage.
他不需要再来一个人质
He doesn't need another hostage.
别这样
Oh, come on!
懂了吗
Yes?
别激怒我  凯文
Don't provoke me, Kevin.
你还剩九根手指头
You still have nine fingers.
这一部分
This section has to do
与针对恶魔的防卫性武器有关
with building defensive weapons against demons.
这个你肯定很熟悉
Mm-hmm. You're familiar with that one, I believe.
这一部分...说的是
And this one... describes...
封印地狱之门
sealing the gates of hell.
这么说是真的  就在那里
So it's true. It's there.
很显然  人类不能拥有这东西
Clearly, humans cannot possess this thing.
神是怎么想的  回头仔细看看
What was god thinking? We'll get back to that.
很快就到有趣的部分了
We're just getting to the sexy part.
很好  我往那边走
All right. I'll check that way.
等等
Hold on.
这个不同  不是信息
This is different. It's -- it's not text.
像是私人笔记
It's like a personal note?
是神的笔记吗
A personal note from god?
是大天使
From... the archangel...
梅塔特隆的
Metatron.
神的书记员
The scribe...
马屁精
...and suck-up.
记录神的口谕  以及帮神擦屁股
Took down god's word, picked up his cleaning.
像是告别的话
It's like a farewell note.
念
Go on.
"等这一任务完成
"Upon completion of this task,
我就告别主人和这个世界"
I take my leave of my master and this world."
温彻斯特
Winchester.
看起来你们注意到我了
Looks like you guys got me.
凯文就在附近
We're very near Kevin.
不
Oh, no.
嗨
Hey.
我是来帮你们的
I'm here to help.
这到底是怎么回事
What the hell's going on?
你没有完全恢复  对吧
You're not all the way back, are you?
"因此不再记录
"So ends the transcription
维护人类的神谕
"of the sacred word for the defense of mankind.
由神之子的手
"Into the hands of god's children
传递石碑目录"
thus passes the compendium of tablets."
-目录  -就是指有一系列的东西
- Compendium? - It's a collection of things,
特别是指有系统有顺序的东西
especially one systematically organized.
我懂这词的意思  凯文
I know what "Compendium" means, Kevin.
梅塔特隆是什么意思
What does Metatron mean?
打不开
It's not working.
迪恩  我进去了
Dean, I'm going in.
不  小卡  你不够强
Cass, no. You're not strong enough.
还有碑文
There are more tablets?
不只是利维坦和恶魔
More than "Leviathan" And "Demon"?
卡西迪奥
Castiel.
刚从炼狱回来啊
Fresh from purgatory.
你应该先打个电话嘛
I wish you'd called first.
克劳力
Crowley.
这次是哪个卡西迪奥  我总是搞不清楚
Which Castiel is it this time? I'm never sure.
疯子  还是自大狂
Madman or megalomaniac?
凯文要跟我走
Kevin is coming with me.
不可能
I think not.
先知在我这边玩呢
The prophet's playing on my team now.
所以只能这样了吗
So this is how it's gonna be?
非常像《西区故事》  但是我们都理智点
It's all very West Side Story, but let's be logical.
你看起来很糟  我应该知道
You look like hell, and I should know.
你并没有准备好呢
You're not up for this.
也许你能点燃  但是你无法保持住
Maybe you can get it up, but you can't keep it up.
你在虚张声势
You're bluffing!
你想冒险一试吗
Do you want to take that chance?
警察很快就到
Cops are on their way.
他们要接上先知
They're gonna pick up the prophets.
他们都会直接回去
Um, they'll all be heading home.
我们呢
What about us?
我打电话叫了我们的朋友  盖思
I called a friend of ours, Garth.
他和我们一样处理这些事
He does what we do.
只是他有自己的方式
Well...in his own way.
他会照顾你们
He'll keep an eye on you guys.
不要再独自行动了
No more going off on your own.
你知道是因为雇了那个巫师
You get that it was hiring that witch
才让你们卷入这一切的吧
that got you into all this, right?
凯文  还撑得住吗
How you holding up, Kev?
你开玩笑吧
You kidding?
我想要把这些混蛋永远封住
I want to seal those bastards up forever.
砍了我的手指
Took my finger.
小卡认为他也许有办法治好
Cass thinks he might be able to fix that.
在此期间保持低调  等我们再来找你  好吗
In the meantime, just lay low till we get back to you, okay?
刚刚你那么做真是笨蛋一个
That was a bonehead move back there.
你可能会把自己害死
You could have gotten yourself killed.
为什么不等我
Why didn't you wait for me?
我没死  而且方法有效
Well, I didn't get killed. And it worked.
如果没效果呢
And if it didn't?
那也是我的问题
It would have been my problem.
我可不觉得
Well, that's not the way I see it.
不是一切事情都需要你负责
Hey, everything isn't your responsibility.
把我带出炼狱也不是你的职责
Getting me out of purgatory wasn't your responsibility.
你没能出来  那是谁的错
You didn't get out. So whose fault was it?
这无关对错  都是意志问题
It's not about fault. It's about will.
迪恩  你真的不记得了吗
Dean, do you really not remember?
小卡  我在那里呆过
I lived it, Cass.
好嘛  我知道发生了什么
Okay, I know what happened.
不  你以为你知道
No. No, you think you know.
其实只是以你需要的方式记忆而已
You remembered it the way you needed to.
我不需要因为遗弃你而感到痛苦
Look, I don't need to feel like hell for failing you, okay?
遗弃你就像是失去了每一件我在乎的事情
For failing you like I've failed every other godforsaken thing that I care about!
我不需要
I don't need it!
迪恩  你看看
Dean. Just look at it.
认真看看
Really look at it.
小卡  该死  加油
Cass! Damn it! Come on!
快来
Come on!
我抓住你了  坚持住
I got you! Hold on!
迪恩
Dean!
坚持住
Hold on!
迪恩
Dean!
快走
Go!
看见了吧  并不是因为我当时太虚弱
See, it wasn't that I was weak.
我当时比你还强壮
I was stronger than you.
我挣脱开的
I pulled away.
你做什么也没办法救下我
Nothing you could have done would have saved me,
因为我根本不想被拯救
because I didn't want to be saved.
你到底在说什么
What the hell are you talking about?
我属于那里
It's where I belonged.
我需要苦行赎罪
I needed to do penance.
就在我在人间和天堂所做的一切之后
After the things I did on earth and in heaven,
我不配离开
I didn't deserve to be out.
我在里面的时候就清楚认识到了
And I saw that clearly when I was there.
我...
I...
我计划一直待在里面
I planned to stay all along.
我只是不知道要如何告诉你
I just didn't know how to tell you.
我的朋友  你不可能救下所有人
You can't save everyone, my friend...
尽管  你一直努力着
Though, you try.
没事吧
Everything okay?
没事
Yeah.
只是  把一些事情说清楚
Just, uh... setting a few things straight.
很好  盖思会低调地...
Good. Garth is gonna lay low with the tra...
你好  卡西迪奥
Hello, Castiel.
我在哪儿
Where am I?
你不知道吗
You don't know?
你在家里  卡西迪奥
You're home, Castiel.
天堂
Heaven?
我从没来过这里
I've never been here before.
没多少天使来过
Not many have.
我叫娜奥米
My name is Naomi.
我们救了你
We rescued you.
从炼狱
Purgatory?
派天使入侵  这让我们失去了不少生命
An incursion of angels, which cost us many lives.
把我们的对话当做是你的报答
Consider these chats your repayment.
我不理解
I don't understand.
和我说说萨姆和迪恩吧
Tell me about Sam and Dean.
先知现在很安全
The prophet is being kept safe.
石碑裂成了两块
The tablet has split in two
温彻斯特兄弟试图找回丢失的那块
and the Winchesters are trying to recover the missing piece.
我为什么要告诉你这些
Why am I telling you any of this?
不需要你操心
It's not your concern.
帮助温彻斯特兄弟  他们找你就出来
Help the Winchesters, come when they call.
你要定期向我汇报
You will report in to me regularly,
但是你永远不会记得你这么做过
and you will never remember having done so.
是的  不会记住
No. I won't do that.
现在  回去吧
Now, as you were.
他们都不会注意你消失了一会
They won't even notice you were gone.
去寻找另外一块
...track down the other piece.
你这次会帮我们的  小卡  对吧
You're with us on this one, right, Cass?
小卡  你没事吧
Cass, you okay?
我没事
I'm -- I'm fine.
是的  我帮你们  如果没问题的话
And, yes, I'm with you -- if that's all right.
没问题  对吧
It is, right?
你们俩没事吧
You two are good?
没事
Yeah.